when you ask someone what defines their
life they'll tell you stories about
their relationships the ones they love
the ones who love them they'll tell you
about the special moments they've had
together the memories they've made and
the indelible impact they've had on
their life you hear about what they
believe in and about their passions and
the qualities that made them special a
hard worker
always optimistic always reliable
always being there with a kind word or
good advice you will hear how they've
made their life better and when you
listen a little harder you'll also hear
about other relationships they have
their relationship with time with
security their health their country
their future
you may hear stories about their sorrows
or fears
but you'll hear many more about the
things that bring them joy our
relationships make us who we are they
make our lives matter
we need others to grow we can't do it
alone
we need valuable relationships so
together let's make life better
Prudential always listening always
understanding